uh if you haven't laughed at all yet I'm
assuming it's just because you're still
trying to figure out ethnically what I
am
describe what this face means is half of
me built the railroads in this country
and the other half
told the first half to do that
my mom hates that joke a lot
that's which one she is
[Applause]
on my white side it's a lot of German
very very German I speak German almost
fluently I speak it I speak it pretty
much fluently so after the show if you
speak German don't talk to me because
I'm lying but
I speak it pretty fluently and I love
the language I think it gets a bad rap
because here they just show us German
propaganda basically like they all sound
like mean when you listen to the
language it's kind of nice and also
their language gives you an insight into
how they think the efficiency literal
that's very German for example look at
the look at the translations from
English to German literally and you will
see how German minds work all right we
say things in our language in English
like have fun right that's what you guys
are doing now fun is just something you
can have you want some fun here here
take some oh look I found some fun back
here you want it go take it
which literally translates to make fun
because you're not allowed to just have
fun in general you think you can just
have the fun lying around are your
things the fun just girls on the fun
tree and then you're just plans of fun
for you like a little fun monkey who
grabs the fun fruit this is delicious
fun fruit and the fun juice drips down
the function and the fun chest until the
fun ground
who sings that tells us worse you didn't
even plant that fun seed is that someone
else is it groomed as a country and you
stole the fun for do I have fun thief
and you steal fun
that is who you are
I wouldn't put it past a German person
to go to a little girl like
four-year-olds for a birthday party be
like you little girl what is all this
ribbons cake presents all for you for
fun
you know the only person who made fun on
this day who did work on this day your
mother this iPad is hers now thank you
very much
here you go Mama have fun with Candy
Crush you here's a stick here's a knife
go vit or something make some fun
what's your high score
my mom is a immigrant fresh off the boat
from Hong Kong she's Chinese
in case you didn't get the railroad
thing um
and I feel for her because she told me a
lot of like you know moving to the
Midwest he told me a lot of like horror
stories about the racism she had to
encounter when she was here so I was
fully on board with the stop Asian hate
movement like I was 100 on board with it
and my favorite story was about the 76
year old Chinese Grandma who got Blind
Side punched but then grabbed a stick
and beat her assailant into a stretcher
now if you're not clapping laughing and
you didn't like that think about if
someone punched your grandma and then
your grandma just went ramble on them
how would you react
you'd be like yo grandma you got this
I'm gonna hang back
scared of you more than ever
but here's why that's my favorite story
because of that assailant that dude was
a little bit less racist just a little
bit
he would have known that a stick is a
minority grandparent's favorite thing to
beat people with
[Laughter]
what that's her secret weapon
near water
both instances you're punching something
ancient tiny and Asian
that if it touches the thing next to it
has the power to suddenly destroy you
insane do you understand what I'm saying
like this woman's been beaten kids since
the Ming Dynasty you don't think she can
take out a millennial from the Bay Area
that's nothing that is nothing to her
Catholic nuns watch YouTube tutorial
videos of old Asian women just beating
people with six like yo May Ling got
hands
what do you think sister subscribe yeah
I got this
I don't even think she picked up the the
stick I think she got punched landed and
then like Thor's hammer she just reached
down
freeway
May link to life
the only thing that would have made this
story any better the only thing is if
she would have handled the interview
afterwards like a pro athlete
because she was you know quavering she's
an old lady but that would have been
awesome is if the reporter came up was
just like so how did you fight off
someone who was bigger faster and
stronger than you and she just stole the
mic out of the hand and it was like
anything about the size of the dog into
fight it's about the size of the fight
in the dog just drop the mic drop the
stick off to the locker room they Lings
out
[Applause]
[Music]
but because I grew up in the midwest you
know I wish I just wish I knew more
about my Chinese Heritage you know what
I mean I don't know as much as I want to
but I do know that whoever invented Tai
Chi was just the best at not touching
things in public restrooms
and apparently we all learn from the
same Master right the same Shifu the
same Sensei because we all do the same
thing and if you don't agree with me
you're lying this is any of us trying to
get out of a public restroom Stone all
right I'm good
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
my God
made it
[Music]
[Applause]
oh my phone I gotta go back in that's
what I get for tweeting on the toilet
[Music]
that's how Tai Chi was invented it
wasn't one Asian monk who trained in the
mountains for 20 years it was one
trucker who stopped at a Pilot station
in Colorado
is this like not today use Band-Aid get
out of my face getting out of here
unscathed
it's weird people forget people forget
Coldspring Heritage are different right
I mean Heritage is just you know your
blood who you are you might be a little
Irish a little Scottish little you know
German Chinese whatever you are but your
culture is like who you grew up around
and I think that influences who you are
more than anything right your friends
your family the people you're with right
now it's your culture in Indianapolis it
was all black and white people so I
consider myself very culturally black
and white you know I talk very white
around white people as you can tell
and I talk very black around black
people
always in awkward silence every show
I've done every time I say that
I don't care judge me all you want those
are my friends and family I don't even
care you can judge me all right I say
things like fidna
I'm fin to go do some comedy um
when I want someone to repeat something
I say give it to me one Mogan
and they usually do
uh
and most importantly when I want to get
at the end of a story but I don't feel
like telling the middle of the story I
say things like woo-woo to propel me to
the end of that story
foreign
people let me explain
um
woo-woo is just the Black version of the
phrase one thing led to another that's
all that is it's just to take up 80 of a
middle of a story you don't feel like
telling here's a black Daytona story hey
man me and my boys cruising up to this
club and Austin is like you say ah and I
was like
and then I fell off a bridge and you're
like
you don't want to clear up the middle of
that you went to a club and then bridge
falling off that's how that story went
it was a book it'd be prologue epilogue
end of book
why are they building bridges near clubs
what are you what city are you in
you just never know
as a matter of fact that's how I thought
Obama should have just pacified white
people who didn't like him in his
speeches to just confuse them and leave
how gray was that event he just goes up
there uh listen
uh now they questioned My Healthcare
and you know what they the question my
birth certificate as well
and uh you know to those people
yeah I just have uh one thing to say
we'll legalize gay marriage thank you
very much
[Applause]
we'd all been like I don't know what his
platform is but I'm voting for this guy
I didn't understand anything and the
best part is they would have to teach
that to your kids in history classes
later some social studies teacher would
have been looking at your kids like turn
to page four and in 2012 Obama enacted
the woohoo act as a legitimate defense
in a court of law turn to page five
the weird thing is the only people that
ever gave me any grief for talking like
that were not black people it was white
people and I was like you don't have a
dog in this fight that you can't get
offended on someone else's behalf it
doesn't make sense my black friends
didn't care they just knew that was me
being me and I think they understood it
was a sign of respect really think about
it if someone from another country came
to this one and asked you for directions
and whatever your his accent is I don't
know how you get to the corner of the
street and you just rattle off fluent
English it's going to be too much
overload for they're gonna be like I
don't understand
yeah no slow down please but if you look
them dead in the eyes and talk to them
just like them and you're like yes you
do go to this corner of the street and
you take the street left and there's
four right then you go backwards in the
fourth they're gonna be like you are
best American I understand everything
between everything this way right yeah
if you don't believe me I have to do
that to my own mom
I know I'm right about this I'm just
like yeah Mom you're cooking just take
the chicken put it in 300 degrees for 30
minutes she's like I don't and I'm like
put it in at 300 degrees for 13 minutes
she's like gotcha
[Applause]
that's why I don't even think you should
teach foreign languages in schools
anymore you should just teach broken
English and other people's accents
[Applause]
why not Spanish 101 course today class
we're covering confrontations repeat
after me that's not yours Holmes now you
go
[Applause]
very good class A Plus dismissed early
let's go home
I think